[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "கிடங்கு",
    "answers": ["கிடங்கு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "நிர்ணயம்",
    "answers": ["நிர்ணயம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "நாற்றம்",
    "answers": ["நாற்றம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "கலக்கம்",
    "answers": ["கலக்கம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "துரும்பு",
    "answers": ["துரும்பு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "மனச்சுமை",
    "answers": ["மனச்சுமை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "புறங்கை",
    "answers": ["புறங்கை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "முரண்பாடு",
    "answers": ["முரண்பாடு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "நோயாளி",
    "answers": ["நோயாளி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "பொம்மை",
    "answers": ["பொம்மை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "மெத்தை",
    "answers": ["மெத்தை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "சன்னல்",
    "answers": ["சன்னல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "திரைச்சீலை",
    "answers": ["திரைச்சீலை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "மின்விசிறி",
    "answers": ["மின்விசிறி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "பூங்கொத்து",
    "answers": ["பூங்கொத்து"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "செய்தித்தாள்",
    "answers": ["செய்தித்தாள்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "தண்ணீர்",
    "answers": ["தண்ணீர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "மேசை",
    "answers": ["மேசை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "நகப்பூச்சு",
    "answers": ["நகப்பூச்சு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "பாரம்பரியம்",
    "answers": ["பாரம்பரியம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "அரசாங்கம்",
    "answers": ["அரசாங்கம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "இளவேனில்",
    "answers": ["இளவேனில்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "மழைமேகம்",
    "answers": ["மழைமேகம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "வெப்பநிலை",
    "answers": ["வெப்பநிலை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "புயல்காற்று",
    "answers": ["புயல்காற்று"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "கூடைப்பந்து",
    "answers": ["கூடைப்பந்து"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  }
]
